tweakandtrick.com 2015-06-07

# Privacy Policy and Terms of Use

Privacy Policy

_We value your privacy and hence, do all that is possible to protect it. This document describes in detail what information do we collect from you and how we use it._

**What information do we collect when you register on our site?**

We collect information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter. 

When registering on our site, you will be asked to enter your mailing address. When commenting on our website, you will be asked to enter your name. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

**Why do we need your email address?**

; To send emails

> The email address you provide us will only be used to send you updates whenever we publish a new post.

You will be able to unsubscribe at anytime using the link given at the end of each message you receive.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. ****

**Third party products, links and services**

We may include or offer third party links, products or services on our website. These third party sites have individual privacy policies. We have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these third party products and websites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, we make use of log files. These files merely logs visitors to the site - usually a standard procedure for hosting companies and a part of hosting services's analytics. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. This information is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

**Do we use cookies?**

We use cookies to store information about visitors' preferences, to record user-specific information on which pages the site visitor accesses or visits, and to personalize or customize our web page content based upon visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' website.

Terms of Use

While every effort has been made to make sure that information provided on this website is accurate, the information is provided on an **AS IS** basis without any liability whatsoever. By using this site, you agree that TweakAndTrick.com or any of its owners will not be held responsible for any losses occurred by your reading or use of this site. You also agree that you bear the full responsibility of any harm that occurs to you or anyone else because of you by your use of information or applications provided on this site.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy and terms of use.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy and Terms of Use**

This document is subject to change without prior notice and changes will be effective immediately. In case of any issue, the latest version of this document will be used. If we decide to change our policies, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Policy modification date below. 

This policy was last modified on 1 July 2014.

**Contacting Us**

You can contact us regarding this policy by using our [contact form](http://www.tweakandtrick.com/2011/02/contact.html) or sending an email to [tweakandtrick@gmail.com](mailto:tweakandtrick@gmail.com).
